stuffpoint.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy

### What Our Privacy Policy Covers

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Stuffpoint.com ("Stuffpoint") or by third-party advertisers (together, the "Third-Parties" or individually a "Third-Party" );
  2. How the information is used;
  3. How you can access and change your account information;
  4. How you will receive notice of changes in this privacy policy; and
  5. How to contact Stuffpoint.

### Information Collected by Stuffpoint

To become a member of Stuffpoint, you must join and create an account on the Stuffpoint website. The only information that Stuffpoint collects is the information you provide through the Stuffpoint registration process, and the information you provide when you update your payment options. This information includes your first and last name, your email address, your Internet Protocol Address ("IP address"), and other contact information. Your IP address is recorded when you register, so that Stuffpoint can enforce its one account per person policy and other provisions of our Terms of Service.

Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Stuffpoint from the website (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization), and it is exclusively owned by Stuffpoint. This information can be utilized by Stuffpoint in such manner as Stuffpoint, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

### Information Sharing & Disclosure

Stuffpoint will not share your personal information with the Third-Parties for the purpose of advertising, i.e. sending unsolicited email. Your email address will be used, however, for tracking purposes, when you complete offers, so that Stuffpoint can determine that you completed the offers. Stuffpoint will also use your email address to send you the Stuffpoint newsletters, unless you have opted out of receiving such newsletters by so indicating on the "E-mail Options" section of the "My Account" page, within the "Members Area" of the Stuffpoint website.

### Information Provided to Third-Parties or Other Users

Stuffpoint.com ("Stuffpoint") deals in large part with the Third-Parties. You may be asked by the Third-Parties to give them your personally identifiable information, either when you complete an offer, when you use their websites, or by some other means. Stuffpoint is not responsible for information you provide the Third-Parties, and you should read their privacy policies as well before providing them with any such information. Please note, unless otherwise stated, any offer you complete on Stuffpoint.com will be with a Third-Party.

Any information you post on the Stuffpoint website or send through Stuffpoint's Message Center may be available to other Stuffpoint users or viewers of the Stuffpoint website. Stuffpoint is not responsible for the information you post on the Stuffpoint website or for information you provide other Stuffpoint users, all of which you do at your own risk.

### Legal Disclaimer

It is possible that Stuffpoint may need to disclose your personally identifiable information from time to time. Specifically, Stuffpoint may disclose any information it has about you to legal authorities, your Internet Service Provider, or other harmed parties without your prior permission, if Stuffpoint has a good-faith belief that such disclosure is warranted and/or necessary because: (1) you have violated Stuffpoint's Terms of Service, (2) you have undertaken actions which are illegal, fraudulent, or otherwise harmful to Stuffpoint, its users, or the Third-Parties, or such disclosure is necessary (3) to conform to legal requirements or to comply with the legal process, (4) to protect and defend Stuffpoint's rights in any legal, judicial or administrative proceeding; or (5) to enforce the Terms of Service.

### Managing Your Information

You can review the personal information you have provided Stuffpoint and make any desired changes to that information by logging in to your account on the Stuffpoint website, clicking on the "My Account" icon in the "Members Area" section of the Stuffpoint website, by editing the information, and then by submitting the revised information. You should update Stuffpoint on any changes that occur, which would make the information you have provided Stuffpoint inaccurate or misleading.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable information may be used or shared will be emailed to you or posted on the Stuffpoint website. Your continued use of the Stuffpoint program after such notices of changes have been sent to you or published on the Stuffpoint website constitutes your consent to the changes.

### Third party sites

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

### Questions & Comments

Unless stated otherwise, Stuffpoint's current privacy policy applies to all information that Stuffpoint has about you and your account. If you have any questions or comments regarding your privacy or this privacy policy, you should contact Stuffpoint prior to providing Stuffpoint any personally identifiable information.

| 

advertisement

### What is Stuffpoint?

Register! Learn More? Login?

### recent images

### recent forum posts

### browse clubs

| Animals| Anime  
---|---  
Arts| Books  
Cars| Celebrities  
Characters| Comics  
Culture| Fashion  
Food & Drink| Games  
Hobbies| Internet  
Movies| Music  
Other| Sports  
Television| Travel  
  
Connect With Us
